# Tiamo **Idzenga**

#### CLOUD ENGINEER · ZAANSTAD

### Summary.

Azure certified Cloud Engineer who believes software should be reliable, manageable and secure to continuously deliver the best quality for your users. I have experience designing, implementing and managing architecture for complex systems in the cloud; developing (web)applications and developing and managing (REST) API's.

## Work Experience \_\_\_\_

A&A Capacity Zaanstad, The Netherlands

CLOUD ENGINEER

Sep. 2020 - Feb. 2022

- Writing a bachelor thesis about cloud computing, performing research into system integration in on-premise, hybrid and cloud environments
  and advising a cloud migration strategy to bring current business operations to Microsoft Azure
- Developing a software solution using the .NET Core Templating Engine to generate Azure applications (including CI/CD system and IaC solution) modularly containing multiple pre-configured integrations to several Azure services including authentication, integration and monitoring
- · Bearing responsibility for the DevOps side of systems, managing cloud infrastructure, CI/CD pipelines and monitoring applications
- Developing custom applications for enterprise clients utilising a .NET and Azure stack, focusing primarily on the cloud native aspects such as architecture and implementing integrations to cloud services
- Developing (automated) testing suites and packages for REST API's and other applications

Creative Skills Zaanstad, The Netherlands

WEB DEVELOPER (PART-TIME)

Jul. 2019 - Jan 2020

 Developing multiple custom made web applications, CMS and packages for (primarily) clients in the e-commerce sector using Laravel, Backpack and PostgreSQL or MySQL

#### **Copernicus Interchange Technology**

Schiphol, The Netherlands

WEB DEVELOPER (INTERNSHIP)

Feb. 2019 - Jul. 2019

- Developed a full stack web application using Laravel and MySQL for a hospital performing a population screening as part of a PhD research
  publication into kidney failure preventing kidney transplantation and dialysis treatments in thousands of patients by preliminary screening
  population with risk factors
- · Implemented a secure environment for patient data utilising the protected KPN E-Zorg network

GIN Masternode Platform

Bucharest, Romania

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Mav. 2018 - Oct. 2018

- Developed a strategy in cooperation with the founders for a cryptocurrency service empowering investors looking for ROI to host masternodes in a few clicks for a monthly fee paid in our own cryptocurrency GIN
- Developed a MVP consisting of a back-end utilising K8S and Docker to spin up virtual machines in a public cloud environment hosting masternodes within minutes and a front-end web application utilising the MEAN stack bringing our service to market within a month
- · Grew our service to several thousands of customers over the coming months, managing millions of dollars worth of collateral
- Launched my own community GIN Shared Nodes of over 500 investors, managing over a hundred shared masternodes worth up to \$500.000 in shared masternode investments for several cryptocurrencies
- Developed my own Node.js back-end for GIN Shared Nodes to automate investor deposits, withdrawals, replacements of stakes and reward payments

#### **Education**

Hogeschool Inholland

Haarlem, The Netherlands

B.Sc Information Technology

2021

- Finished with thesis: "Modular System Integration Solutions in the Cloud", 8
- Minors: Cloud Computing & Security and User Experience Design (UXD)
- Extracurricular activities: member of study association Lepidoptera, class representative, participator in the "buddy-system" for international students, mentor on introduction week, teaching programming classes

# **Certifications**

Nov. 2021 Microsoft Certified: Azure Developer Associate, AZ-204

DECEMBER 6, 2021 TIAMO IDZENGA · CV 1